ZARA YUJUNG CHEN

zarayujungchen-strategicdesign.com









STRATEGY

347 - 283 - 7646 itszarachen@gmail.com zarayujungchen-strategicdesign.com

Industrial designer specializing in display design and project management. Professional experience includes product design from inception to end product. Worked for one of the top global makeup brands to understand and visually communicate the brand culture through display products strategically placed within its market. Master degree in Design Management, bridging the gap between business and design.

SKILLS



3D SOFTWARE



2D SOFTWARE

INDUSTRIAL DESIGN

COMMUNICATION DESIGN

DESIGN THINKING

BUSINESS STRATEGY Alias, Showcase, Pro E, 3D CAD, 3D MAX, Solidworks, Rhino, SketchUp, KeyShot

Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, iMovie, Keynote, Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Research, Human Factors, Materials, Product forming, Sketch, Prototyping, Manufacturing Process

Brand Identity, Logo Design, Package Design, Infographics, Video Editing, Web Design

Brainstorming, Problem Solving, Strategic Design, Sustainable Design

Market Analysis, Financial Report, Strategic Business, Operation Management, Employee Engagement, Public Relations



EXPERIENCE

MAC COSMETICS

Industrial Designer Oct 2015 - present

HAIR PHILOSOPHY **NEW YORK**

Brand Designer May 2015 - Sep 2015

FRANCIS PASTRY SHOP

Brand Designer & Strategist June 2012 - July 2013

FREELANCE

Graphic and Package Designer January 2011 - Oct 2015

PROCESS BRAND **EVOLUTION**

Intern July 2011 - November 2011

CSS GROUP

Graphic Designer January 2011 - July 2011 Overseeing Permanent Displayer category for all store formats nationally and globally. Designing and managing launch displayers, special displayers, multi-channel gondolas, package design and store fixtures. Communicating cross departments and vendors. Presenting design concept and prototype to senior management.

Designed brand Identity system, website, package and products.

Executed market analysis, brand positioning analysis, brand identity design, planned, designed and oversaw the store decorations, meals display and related products design.

Designed brand identity, primary and secondary package and marketing materials for brands in beauty, food, hospitality, education and real estate industry.

Reviewed marketing trends, executed daily operations, market analysis, customers' company internal and external situation analysis, and created design to achieve customer needs.

Company brand identity, created presentation material, product, service and infographic.

EDUCATION

PRATT INSTITUTE Design Management, Master of Professional Studies, 2015



SCHOOL OF VISUAL ARTS

Brand Identity, Continuing Education Course, 2014



SHIH CHIEH UNIVERSITY

Industrial and Product Design, Bachelor of Art, 2011



AWARDS

REDDOT AWARD

Germany, 2012 Best of the Best Award reddot design award best of the best 2012



YOUNG DESIGNERS' DESIGN COMPETITION

Taiwan, 2011 Outstanding Performance Award



EXHIBITIONS

REDDOT AWARD

Singapore, 2012

NAKANOSHIMA OSAKA DESIGN **CRAFT EXHIBITION**

Osaka, Japan, 2011

YOUNG DESIGNERS' **DESIGN COMPETITION**

Taipei, Taiwan, 2011

CREATIVITY FAIR

Xiamen, China, 2009



PATENT

MULTIFUNCTIONAL SLEEPING BAG

Taiwan U-4580-1

MULTIFUNCTIONAL SLEEPING BAG

China CN 202959281 U



LANGUAGE

FTSANY TAIWANESE **ENGLISH** Proficiency **CHINESE** Proficiency



AEDA (Asia Experience Design Association) Event & Community Team Leader May 2016 - Present

STUDENT ASSOCIATES Vice President May 2014 - May 2015